

#### **CONTACT ME AT**

- wendellchansuazo11@gmail.com
- 09959768531
- https://wendell-suazo.netlify.app/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/wendell-suazo-8339251aa/
- blk. 26 Lot 17, GK Village, Majada In, Canlubang, Calamba City, Laguna

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Software Development
- ●●●● HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap
- •••• Javascript, Jquery, AJAX
- •••• PHP, Laravel, MYSQL, GIT, Github

#### AWARDS RECEIVED

- President Lister Polytechnic University of the Philippines
   Oct 2019 - March 2022
- Computer Specialist of the Year -Majada In Integrated School Mar 2016
- Class Valedictorian Majada In Elementary School 2009 - 2010 Grade 4 - Grade 6
- First Honor Majada In Elementary School 2008 - 2010 Grade 4 - Grade 6
- First Honor San Cristobal Elementary School 2005 - 2007 Grade 2 – Grade 3

# WENDELL SUAZO

# FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

#### PROFILE SUMMARY

I've been practicing and honing my skills in different programming languages such as javascript, php and mysql. As well as different web frameworks/tools/plugins like laravel, bootstrap, jquery, and SASS. I am trying to dive as deep as I can to these web technologies to use it's full potential.

I am also doing freelance work that helps me earn at the same time learn by experience.

I can do frontend and backend to develop different applications for both professional and personal use.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Freelance Web-Developer

Jan. 2021- present

Create web applications for clients depending on their needs

## **Backend Developer**

IThinkWeb Corporation | July 2021- Jan. 2022

- Managed complex projects from start to finish
- Created API endpoints for frontend to consume
- Collaborated with other developers

#### EDUCATION

- Polytechnic University of the Philippines
   Bachelor of Science in Information Technology
   2018 2022
- STI College Calamba
   IT and Mobile App Development, Information Technology
   2016 2018
- Graduated senior high school in STI College Calamba with Technical Vocational strand specializing in IT and Mobile App Development
- Majada In Integrated School 2012 – 2016 Junior High School
- Majada In Elementary School 2008 – 2012 Elementary School
- San Cristobal Elementary School 2004 – 2008 Elementary School

# NOTABLE PROJECTS

#### ■ CALAMBA ENTREP ONLINE STORE

Calamba Entrep is an online marketplace where anyone can sell, buy, and discover one-of-a-kind products. We stand behind our merchants & their products. We're also a community working to make a difference for small businesses.

Technology used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, PHP, MYSQL, Laravel, Laravel-livewire, Vue Js

# **■ TECH2U COMPUTER REPAIR SERVICE**

Tech2U Computer Repair Service is a place for you to to fix your computers and cellphone gadgets at affordable and reasonable price. We've been repairing broken or corrupted electronic gadgets. Whether your device fell on concrete or water, we'll make sure it will run again in its best condition.

Technology used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, PHP/Laravel 7, Laravel-livewire, MYSQL

#### ■ ENRICO MERCHANDISE

An Eccommerce Web application made mainly using Laravel 7 as server-side language. The customer has the ability to add to cart the selected items, checkout and pay using Cash on Delivery(COD) or through PAYPAL. The system also offers complete administration panel and users are divided into several roles/privelages such as admin, product manager and customer.

Technology used:HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, PHP/Laravel 7, MYSQL

# CERTIFICATIONS

### CYBERSECURITY ESSENTIALS- ISSUED BY CISCO

The holder of this credential has a foundational knowledge of cybersecurity, including the basics of network security, DevSecOps (Development, Security, Operations), encryption and cybersecurity laws. The holder has been introduced to tactics and techniques used by Black Hats, and the principles of Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability (CIA) used by White Hats to defend networks. This credential also certifies that the holder has practiced critical thinking and problem solving skills.

https://www.credly.com/badges/87fae324-d3e7-49ad-b65f-4e70ec7f90cf?source=linked\_in\_profile

#### ■ INTRODUCTION TO CYBERSECURITY- ISSUED BY CISCO

The holder of this credential has introductory knowledge of cybersecurity, including the global implications of cyber threats, the impact of cyber attacks on industries, and why cybersecurity is a growing profession. The holder has an understanding of the ways in which networks are vulnerable to attack and Cisco's approach to threat detection and defense. They also have insight into opportunities available for pursuing network security certifications.

https://www.credly.com/badges/4c14a57b-c098-4ef9-9072-f1376cc0b1d1?source=linked\_in\_profile